[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Green Square"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Sara, where are you and what's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "We are in Green Square, that the rebels are now calling Martyr Square.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Do they believe he may have escaped the country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "It depends on who you ask, Wolf.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What are your thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "My thoughts, I'm so grateful for this day -- the end of tyranny, the end of brutal dictatorship, the beginning of a new universe, a new horizon for Libya.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Do you intend to go back yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "And what would you like to see happen to Gadhafi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I would like him really to get caught and be put on trial, because a lot of Libyans who suffered under Gadhafi -- who he has killed, maimed, brutalized.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Has this been the best day of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "It's the beginning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What has been your view from the White House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, Piers, it's really nice to be with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Or how they may be getting him away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "We're hearing all sorts of rumors but we try not to focus on rumors on here but rather on facts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["TNC"], "PERSON": ["Jibril"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "How confident is the White House in the rebels and in the future plan for Libya without Gadhafi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "We've been very gratified to hear the very sound statements from the TNC's leadership, that is to say the opposition group's leadership, including as early as today from one of their ministers, Jibril is his name, gave a very good set of comments about the kind of inclusive government they see going forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["Libya"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "How confident are you guys that in the short to midterm, the stability of the region will be stabilized and not, in fact, further endangered by instability of him actually going after so long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Well, I think what we've seen, obviously, is that his ruthless ways did not bring stability, but a great deal of instability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Or would his death be a preferred option?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, the important thing here, Piers, is that we're not in a position to decide that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What is the end game for Gadhafi personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, I think he -- we talked about this yesterday.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "What is your view and assessment of what exactly may be happening now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, what the family wanted was some type of exit strategy and they didn't have that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Is this all just bluff, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I think a lot of it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NTC"], "PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Because of that, can we have more confidence that the NTC will do a good job here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, the leadership of the NTC, of course, are primarily former Gadhafi loyalists.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NTC"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Were you always confident that this day would come?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Do you -- does your client, for example, concede that he behaved inappropriately, if not in any criminal way, but just inappropriately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I think what we said from the beginning, there was an act in that room that was consensual, not forcible and I think we're going to leave it at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "LOCATION": ["Rikers Island"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What is your view of how the legal system people like Dominique Strauss-Kahn before they are being convicted of anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, it's difficult to celebrate entirely on a day like today, when it wasn't three months ago when he was in Rikers Island in an orange jumpsuit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique Strauss-Kahn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique Strauss-Khan", "Anne Sinclair"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "But how -- how has this manifested itself on their relationship, your client and his wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I said outside court today -- and I'll repeat it again -- that unless you yourself have been accused falsely of a serious crime that you did not commit, I think it's impossible to really understand the full measure of relief that Dominique Strauss-Khan and Anne Sinclair felt today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Taylor"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "In particular, there were headlines in some of the daily tabloids, \"Le Perv,\" playing off his French background, and off the supposition that he was obviously guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I think the media is partially at fault in this rush to judgment that Mr. Taylor spoke about earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Mr. Taylor, how would you describe Dominique Strauss-Khan's mood today, after all of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "He is certainly happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Taylor", "Dominique Strauss-Khan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Taylor"], "LOCATION": ["France"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Are you worried about any of these kind of cases now progressing against him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I think, with respect to questions involving allegations in France, I am going to turn to my partner, Bill Taylor, who has dealt with those issues primarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Does he have a sense of regret personally about his actions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I think what we don't do in the United States of America is prosecute people criminally for behavior that someone else might find to be either inappropriate or offensive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Is he keen to get back in the fray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't think he's had an opportunity to think that through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What has been the financial cost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, the financial cost has been enormous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "What was your reaction to that specific claim?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "It's absolutely false.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "What would your client's view of his accuser be today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I think collectively we view her as either evil or pathetic or both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Because surely it can't not be factored in that this has collapsed today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "When did you first meet Jon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Careful.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Did you think you were marrying the next Freddy Mercury?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "You ride Harleys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Forty year ride, 40 year motorcycles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Why should he be president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Because I think he's the greatest leader out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Utah"]}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What is your great master plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "The principles are the same, whether in Utah or whether on a national basis.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Why would you vote against that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I'm not the compromise guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "What was the thinking there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "The thinking there was we had a little more love to give.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Where do you see the line drawn in terms of your adherence to the Mormon faith?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I have a deep belief in God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I'd say, you know, there are 13 million Mormons around the world today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Is that what you're getting at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "You start out by calling me boring.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]